(Leonard:)Be like my Aunt Nancy.
(Leonard:)She had dozens of them.
(Leonard:)And do you know what happened
after she died? They ate her.
(Sheldon:)You don't have to sell
me on cats, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)I'm already a fan.
(Sheldon:)All right, fellas,
who's in the mood for Fancy Feast?
(Sheldon:)Well, that's not fancy at all.
(Leonard:)Hi, Mrs. Cooper. Thanks for coming.
(Mrs Cooper:)Where is he?
(Leonard:)He's in his bedroom.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, when you said on the phone
(Mrs Cooper:)he broke up with a girl,
you meant an actual girl,
(Mrs Cooper:)not something you kids
whipped up in a lab?
(Leonard:)No, she's real.
(Mrs Cooper:)Did they sin?
(Leonard:)No, no, it's not like that.
(Leonard:)It's, uh...
(Leonard:)I don't know what it's like.
(Leonard:)But there is something I
should prepare you for.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, relax, Leonard,
I have raised that boy.
(Mrs Cooper:)I've seen him at his best,
I've seen him at his worst.
(Mrs Cooper:)There's nothing he can
do that'll surprise me.
(Leonard:)Hold on to that thought.